module.exports = [
	{
		answer: "Mean Girls",
		question: "😡 💃 💃 💃 💃 🎅",
	},
	{
		answer: "It",
		question: "🤡 🎈 👿",
	},
	{
		answer: "Ratatouille",
		question: "🐀 🥘 👨‍🍳",
	},
	{
		answer: "Titanic",
		question: "💑 🚢 🥶",
	},
	{
		answer: "Home Alone",
		question: "👦 🏠 🎄",
	},
	{
		answer: "Toy Story",
		question: "👢 🚀 👦",
	},
	{
		answer: "Up",
		question: "🎈 🏠 🎈",
	},
	{
		answer: "Saw",
		question: "🧩🩸 🍥👀🍥",
		alias: ["Jigsaw"],
	},
	{
		answer: "The Godfather",
		question: "💵 🔫 🇮🇹",
		alias: ["Godfather"],
	},
	{
		answer: "Space Jam",
		question: "🪐⛹️‍♂️ 🐰 🐷 🐥",
	},
	{
		answer: "Silence of the Lambs",
		question: "🔇 🐑 🐑 🐑",
	},
	{
		answer: "Jaws",
		question: "🦈 🚣‍♂️",
	},
	{
		answer: "Harry Potter",
		question: "🪄 🧹 ⚡ 👦",
	},
	{
		answer: "500 Days of Summer",
		question: "5️⃣☀️☀️",
	},
	{
		answer: "Scream",
		question: "💀 🔪 ☎️ 😱",
	},
	{
		answer: "The Shining",
		question: "🛎️ 👧🏻 👧🏻 🪓 🚪",
		alias: ["Shining"],
	},
	{
		answer: "Die Hard",
		question: "⚰️ 🪨",
	},
	{
		answer: "La La Land",
		question: "💃 🕺 🌃",
	},
	{
		answer: "Edward Scissorhands",
		question: "👨 ✂️ 👐",
	},
	{
		answer: "The King's Speech",
		question: "👑 🗩",
		alias: ["King's Speech"],
	},
	{
		answer: "Star Wars",
		question: "⭐ ⚔️ 🌌",
	},
	{
		answer: "Clockwork Orange",
		question: "🕰️ 🍊",
	},
	{
		answer: "The Wolf of Wall Street",
		question: "🐺 🏦 💰",
		alias: ["Wolf of Wall Street"],
	},
	{
		answer: "Tooth Fairy",
		question: "🦷🧚",
	},
	{
		answer: "Mad Max",
		question: "🏜️ 😡 🏎️",
	},
	{
		answer: "Minions",
		question: "🍌 🥽 🧤",
	},
	{
		answer: "Night at the Museum",
		question: "🦖 🗿 🔦 🌙",
	},
	{
		answer: "Life of Pi",
		question: "🐅 ⛵",
	},
	{
		answer: "Monsters Inc.",
		question: "👁️ 🚪 🧦",
		alias: ["Monsters Inc", "Monsters Incorporated"],
	},
	{
		answer: "School of Rock",
		question: "🏫 🎸",
	},
	{
		answer: "Four Sisters and a Wedding",
		question: "👭👭💒👰🤵",
		alias: ["4 Sisters and a Wedding"],
	},
];
